let items = [
    {
        number: 1,
        front: "A point inside a parabola that determines its shape",
        back: "Focus"
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        front: "A line outside a parabola that is equidistant to all points on the curve",
        back: "Directrix"
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        front: "(h, k) in the equation y = a(x - h)&sup2 + k",
        back: "Vertex Form"
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        front: "A vertical line passing through the vertex that divides the parabola into two symmetrical halves",
        back: "Axis of Symmetry or Principal Axis"
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        front: "The highest or lowest point on a parabola",
        back: "Vertex"
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        front: "A function of the form f(x) = ax&sup2; + bx + c",
        back: "Quadratic Function"
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        front: "The most general form of a quadratic equation, y = a&sup2 + bx + c",
        back: "Standard Form"
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        front: "Determines the direction and width of the parabola",
        back: "Coefficient"
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        front: "The direction in which the parabola faces",
        back: "Parabola Opening"
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        front: "The property of a parabola where one half is the mirror image of the other",
        back: "Symmetry"
    }
]